<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ready on Terminal</title>
    <link>/tags/ready/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ready on Terminal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/ready/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>/posts/01_04_2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/01_04_2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;afternoon&#34;&gt;Afternoon&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was finally added to CrashCourse&amp;rsquo;s Jellyfin server after two days of waiting. I am excited to get back to watching tv shows or movies at night. I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about Animal Kingdom, crime/drug family running its operation in southern California. Think Son&amp;rsquo;s of Anarchy meets The OC, well that is what I think the show is about. I might finish the Wishmaster movie series, the first one I watched on Youtube and it was funny. Not scary at all, but  does the job of entertaining me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;afternoon&#34;&gt;Afternoon&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was finally added to CrashCourse&amp;rsquo;s Jellyfin server after two days of waiting. I am excited to get back to watching tv shows or movies at night. I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about Animal Kingdom, crime/drug family running its operation in southern California. Think Son&amp;rsquo;s of Anarchy meets The OC, well that is what I think the show is about. I might finish the Wishmaster movie series, the first one I watched on Youtube and it was funny. Not scary at all, but  does the job of entertaining me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My package from GNC came in today containing Ghost energy drink, Barbell protein bar box, and some type of peanut butter protein cookie box. I really want to start hitting my goal of 150g of protein a day. These items will help in adding a bit of variety in hitting that goal over chicken breast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;night&#34;&gt;Night&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Too cold to go to the garage gym today, so I did about 120 reps of dumbbell curls in my room. It was an ok workout, but I need to go to LA Fitness/Xsport and see what their basic plan is. Their online New Years promo is terrible as it is only for the premier plan. If I can&amp;rsquo;t find a gym soon I will have to suck it up and do the garage gym, even if it is 10 degrees outside and the heater doesn&amp;rsquo;t work.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
