<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Moving on Terminal</title>
    <link>/tags/moving/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Moving on Terminal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/moving/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Moving To San Diego In 3 Years</title>
      <link>/posts/01_11_2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/01_11_2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-chat-with-ai&#34;&gt;A Chat With AI&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My desire to move to San Diego (Southern California) has been intensifying recently. I wanted to see what I need to do to be able to move to San Diego in 3 years. I gave ChatGPT my information from a financial and job experience standpoint.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;financial&#34;&gt;Financial&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From a financial standpoint because of my job I am in a pretty good position. I do need to build up an emergency fund, which I was going to do regardless if I was moving to San Diego. The cost of living in Chicago is not that much different from San Diego in terms of apartments. The amenities of the apartment/building might be a little different but that is negated by the fact you are within a walkable distance to the beach in San Diego and the weather is always beautiful.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-chat-with-ai&#34;&gt;A Chat With AI&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My desire to move to San Diego (Southern California) has been intensifying recently. I wanted to see what I need to do to be able to move to San Diego in 3 years. I gave ChatGPT my information from a financial and job experience standpoint.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;financial&#34;&gt;Financial&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From a financial standpoint because of my job I am in a pretty good position. I do need to build up an emergency fund, which I was going to do regardless if I was moving to San Diego. The cost of living in Chicago is not that much different from San Diego in terms of apartments. The amenities of the apartment/building might be a little different but that is negated by the fact you are within a walkable distance to the beach in San Diego and the weather is always beautiful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;job-experience&#34;&gt;Job Experience&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This all comes down to job experience, unfortunately my company doesn&amp;rsquo;t have an office branch in/near San Diego. Working fully remote with my current employer is a possibility, but I don&amp;rsquo;t want to just relay on that. Lucky for me San Diego has a technology sector, specifically in data science. If I can position myself with the data solutions my company has in the first year, it can make me desirable when the time comes to try and find a job in the San Diego job market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Companies to look into are&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Qualcomm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Teradata&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ServiceNow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using my employer&amp;rsquo;s tuition reimbursement benefit to get a Master&amp;rsquo;s in Data Analytics in the 3 years while I prepare myself would be tremendously beneficial.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;scouting&#34;&gt;Scouting&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I need to explore San Diego and other Southern California areas (Oceanside, Orange County). I think the minimum would have to be 2 trips a year to get a sense of the city. Discover the nice areas and the areas to stay away from. Also to discover the businesses that make living in San Diego worthwhile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This requires a lot more information so I will continue this thought in another post.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
